funnierpics.net 2016-12-02

# Privacy - FunnierPics

Updated: April 27, 2016

Your privacy is one of our biggest concerns. Occasionally Funnierpics.com may change its privacy policy. Funnierpics.com encourages visitors to check this page often for any changes to the privacy policy. Continued use of Funnierpics.com websites upon modification to its privacy policy will act as your acceptance of any and all changes.

Intro

Funnierpics.com puts your privacy at the top of our list of priorities.

This privacy policy has been created in accordance with the privacy policy provided by wordpress.com (automattic.com) under the creative commons sharealike license. This notice is very important to any visitor of Funnierpics.com and should be read thoroughly.

Website Visitors and Registered Users

Funnierpics.com collects non-personally-identifying information in a manner similar to many website operators. Information that is typically collected include but are not limited to ones such as the referring site, date and time of visit, browser, operating system, and count of returning versus new visitors. Funnierpics.com uses this information to get a better understanding of their audience and therefore better the website as a whole. Funnierpics.com may publish information to the general public regarding the usage of its website and or affiliate websites but will not release personally-identifying information. Information such as IP addresses or other personally-identifying information may be collected but will not be used to acquire private information on its visitors, nor will it disclose any such information other than described below.

Aggregation of Personally-Identifying Information

A number of visitors to Funnierpics.com decide to interact with the website in a manner where personally-identifiable information is necessary. The amount or type of information that is required will depend upon the form of interaction. In every case, Funnierpics.com will collect such information only as is required or deemed appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Funnierpics.com. Funnierpics.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other then as described below. Visitors have the ability to refuse to provide personally-identifiable information at the risk that they may be prevented from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Aggregated Statistics

Funnierpics.com may analyze and collect statistics about the activities of visitors to its websites. For example, Funnierpics.com may keep account of the most popular pages, collections, or referring sites. Funnierpics.com may display this information publicly or share it with others. Funnierpics.com does not release personally-identifiable information related to its statistics other then as described below.

Protection of Certain Personally-Identifiable Information

Funnierpics.com shares potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know such information to process it on Funnierpics.com’s behalf or to provide services to Funnierpics.com, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose any such information to any other party except for those directly involved. Some of this potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information may be given to parties outside of your country; by using Funnierpics.com websites, you acknowledge and consent to the transfer of such information to them. Also, in some cases we may decide to buy or sell assets. In this type of transaction, information is one of the business assets that is transferred. Additionally, if Funnierpics.com or considerably all of its assets were acquired, or in the unfortunate event that Funnierpics.com goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, use information would be one of the assets that are transferred and or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that this type of transfer may occur, and that any acquirer of Funnierpics.com may continue to use any personal and non-personal information only as set forth in this policy. Otherwise, Funnierpics.com will not lease out, rent, or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Aside from its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as explained in the previous paragraph, Funnierpics.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required by law to do so. Funnierpics.com will also disclose such information when it believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the rights or property of Funnierpics.com, third parties or the general public. Should you be a registered user of a Funnierpics.com website and have supplied your email address, Funnierpics.com may send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit feedback, and or keep you informed of what’s happening with Funnierpics.com and its services. If you send a request to Funnierpics.com either privately or through one of the websites contact tools, Funnierpics.com reserves the right to publish it in order to assist us in clarifying, respond to your request, or to help other users with the same issue. Funnierpics.com ensures that all measures are taken that are reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. Please be aware that if you are submitting information to “chat rooms,” “forums,” “comments” or “message boards” such information is then considered public information. In other words, you lose any and all privacy rights you may have with regards to that information. Doing so also increases the amount of unwanted communications or SPAM.

Cookies

A cookie is information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Funnierpics.com uses cookies to help track and identify visitors, monitor the usage of Funnierpics.com websites and website access preferences every time the visitor returns to the site. Should a visitor refuse to have cookies placed on their computers, the visitor will have to set their browsers to refuse cookies prior to using the Funnierpics.com websites. Users acknowledge and accept that disabling cookies may cause certain features of Funnierpics.com websites to not function properly.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.

Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings.

Advertisements

Ads that appear on any of Funnierpics.com websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may also set cookies. These cookies give the ad server the ability to recognize your computer every time they send you an online advertisement to put together information about you or anyone who uses your computer. This information allows the ad networks to, among other things, deliver advertisements targeted at the user’s interest.

Funnierpics.com ads are serviced by Google Adsense;

Use the following link to access the Google Adsense website for additional information:  http://google.com/adsense;

Visitors of Funnierpics.com may visit Google Adsense to opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising; and

Alternatively, visitors may opt out of third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting aboutads.info.

Third Party Links

This privacy policy applies only to Funnierpics.com and the information that is collected by its websites. This privacy policy does not apply to the conduct of other companies that Funnierpics.com does not own or control, or employees that Funnierpics.com does not manage. Funnierpics.com websites may contain or promote links to other websites. Any information that you provide to, or that is obtained by, third-party organizations or websites may be subject to the privacy policy of those sites, if any at all. Please read the privacy policy of any and all third-party websites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of these third parties to abide by any and all restrictions on the disclosure of your potentially-personally and personally-identifying information. Funnierpics.com and its affiliates shall not be liable for any wrongful use or disclosure of your potentially-identifying and or personally-identifying information by any third party.

Security

All non-personally-identifying information, potentially personally-identifying and personally identifying-information described above is stored on restricted database servers. Funnierpics.com ensures that reasonable measures are taken to ensure the safety of such information.

Choice/Opt-out

If Funnierpics.com contacts you by email concerning new products, services or information that you did not expressly request, Funnierpics.com will provide you with an email address by which you may request no further notices.

Contact

If you have any questions or are unsure about something within the privacy policy, or the Funnierpics.com website itself, please contact us.
